[Music]
awake awake Daniel 12 1-3 The Voice
pierces my ears jolting me out of my
sleep it would normally take me a few
minutes to fully be alert in the morning
but not today unlike anything I've ever
heard this piercing voice resonates deep
within me as I open my eyes I realize I
am in a confined space surrounded by
absolute darkness my heart races and
suddenly thoughts flood my mind my last
memory it seems like just moments ago
were the tear stained faces of family
and my close friends their sorrowful
Embraces and the somber prayers that
were whispered on my behalf as I was yes
I was slipping into death I recall my
last words Lord please save me I
remember that moment as doubts and fears
threatened to consume me how I clung to
my faith that Christ's sacrifice had
indeed covered me that I would stand
before God with peace and live again now
in the darkness a thought takes hold of
me the voice I just heard is it I can
barely finish the thought when suddenly
the confined space begins to shake
violently and I feel an unimaginable
Force pulling me upward the ground
crumbles around me and waves of dust
fill the air propelling me upwards I
feel an Indescribable surge of energy
course through my entire being light
floods my mind as if it is Awakening to
Powers unknown to me before the clarity
of my eyesight stuns me I look at my
hands only to find that they are no
longer the hands I am familiar with 1
Corinthians 15: 50- 54 they glow it is a
radiant light an overwhelming energy
pulsates my entire body I gasp for my
first breath and then I realize I have
been resurrected I've been snatched from
death's Jaws oh death
where is your sting oh grave where is
your Victory my heart shouts 1
Corinthians
15:55 I am aware that my senses have
been
heightened suspended in the air I take
in the incredible sights surrounding me
I look down to see Graves exploding open
and countless people rising from them
their bodies glowing with the same new
found Radiance is mine 1 Thessalonians
4:
13-16 millions of bodies are rejected
from the grave reminding me of Jonah
coming up from the belly of the fish
these are the redeemed from every age
those who died in unwavering faith
believing that Jesus would come again to
rescue them from the clutches of death
John 14 veres 1 to3 I am overwhelmed by
the sheer Beauty and power emanating
from their glorified bodies they look
Regal like an army of kings and
queens all traces of sin death aging
disease are gone a radiant light above
us captures our attention it is Jesus we
all bear a striking resemblance to him 1
John
3:2 he is wrapped in a glorious flame of
Light which brightens the midnight sky
surrounding him is an innumerable
company of Chariots which begin to
streak toward us leaving blazing trails
in the midnight sky Psalms 68 and verse1
17 the this is our Redemption I think to
myself one of the angels of fire is
heading straight toward me the angel
extends its hand to me and I grab hold
of it as this powerful being swings me
up unto his Chariot of fire the fire
does not burn me I have a flashback of
Shadrach mesak and Abednego in the fiery
furnace where the fire had no effect
upon them Daniel 3 I learned that this
is my guardian angel who was
commissioned to be by my side while I
had lived on earth I have many questions
for him but I instinctively know that
this is not the time my eyes sweep the
sky taking in the scene of the multitude
of redeemed Souls suspended midair
glorified then my attention is turned to
the people still standing on the earth
below
us some Have Faces full of dread
Revelation
6:16 While others have faces lighted up
with the glory of God Isaiah 25 and: 9
the same force that pulled us from the
grave now begins to lift these living
Saints into the air I realize that these
are the ones who are alive to see the
Lord's coming and will not taste death
but be translated instead 1
Thessalonians 4:1 17 they too are swept
up by the Chariots their bodies
transformed into Perfection
instantaneously they meet us in the air
and a roar of Triumph erupts from the
mass Army in the sky sky as far as
glorified eyes can see the Horizon is
filled with the followers of Christ like
a massive ring encircling the globe as I
observe the Earth it is apparent that
time has passed at a glance the world
appears more advanced than when I lived
on it a realization hits me I Now
understand that I have been asleep in
the grave for almost two centuries yet
it feels like I was asleep for mere
seconds I remember nothing while I slept
in the grave Ecclesiastes 9: 5 Psalms
115 and: 17 Isaiah 38 and ver1 the
overwhelming peace and relief that fills
my soul cannot be put into words I see
the same looks of ecstatic Joy mirrored
on the faces of my fellow redeemed we
are speeding upward with Christ leading
the way we look back to witness the
Earth becoming desolate before our very
eyes second Peter 3 verse
10-2 Revelation 15 and 16 those who are
not caught up with us are destroyed by
the flood of Christ's fiery Glory just
as it was in the days of Noah Matthew
24:
38-39 not a single person remains alive
on Earth Jeremiah 4:
23-29 Revelation 20: 5 and 6 the
righteous have been caught up in the
clouds while the wicked perish at the
brightness of Jesus they have joined
those left in the grave who had not made
Christ their hope and then a sight on
the earth that causes us to shudder for
the first time our eyes behold the
unveiled Persons Of Satan and his Fallen
Angels so many were led to believe that
he was merely a fictitious figure along
with the Bible itself but now we were
seeing him with our very own eyes as we
begin to move upward an invisible force
appears to change Satan and his angels
onto the earth now desolated by the
glory of God we are told by the angels
that Satan will be bound there for 1,000
years with no one to tempt and that at
the end of the thousand years we will
return at which point Satan will be
loosed and the wicked resurrected for
one final Conflict the battle of
Armageddon Revelation 20: 1-3 and 5-7
our journey into eternity has begun we
are headed to the place Christ has
prepared for us John 14 1-3 Revelation
20 and: 4 as we leave the dark desolated
Earth behind I begin to think of my
loved ones I wonder about my family and
my friends were they left on Earth
destroyed by the overwhelming Glory or
were they among this redeemed Caravan
transformed by
[Music]
it
I scan the immense crowd a Sea of Faces
stretching as far as the eye can see the
sheer scale of this Gathering astounds
me leaving me in awe of the diversity
and Beauty before me each pair of eyes
Tells a Story Each face reflecting a
unique background as we advance towards
the Majestic city of God the crowd stirs
with a palpable energy in this vast
congregation I witness a remarkable
phenomenon unfolding a wave of joyous
recognition ripples through the crowd
like an electric current as a symphony
of reunions plays out before my eyes
loved ones and dear friends long
separated by time distance and death
recognize one another children ripped
from their parents by death are reunited
with them never to be parted
Again In This Crowd no one is a stranger
a loner for us this is a family reunion
every one of us is related by the blood
of Christ the tribes within the tribe of
the redeemed converge creating a
tapestry of love and unity that defies
human
comprehension people from every nation
and tribe are here Revelation 7 and:
9 we recognize Heroes of Faith David
Joshua Abraham Paul and others within
the crowd I wonder what Abraham and
Sarai must be thinking as they look at
the Fulfillment of the promise that
there seed would be as the dust of the
earth and the stars of the sky and now
here we are literally raised Out of the
Dust of the earth and Shining as stars
lighting up the midnight sky Genesis
13:16 Genesis
155 Daniel 12:4 with unyielding
anticipation I searched this multitude
my Gaze fixated on finding my family I
remember countless conversations were
spent envisioning a joyous reunion in
the resurrection
hopeful yet anxious I continue my search
amidst the throng suddenly a moment of
shock hits me a surge of disbelief
floods my being as I realize that my
brother who when I died had not given
his life to the Lord is making his way
towards me how miraculous this moment
feels how unfathomable overwhelmed by an
immeasurable flood of joy we navigate
through the undulating crowd every step
bringing us closer to one another
without disrupting the caravan's
seamless Unity tears of joy flow
relentlessly down our cheeks for we know
that this encounter was possible only
because of Christ yet as I embrace him I
can't help but wonder about the hows and
wise behind his being here my heart
swells with anticipation knowing that we
will have ample time to share and
discover the miraculous transformation
his life must have undergone but the
joyous reunion does not end here for my
eyes soon fall upon the rest of my
family my parents resplendant in
Heavenly Glory stand beside my other two
siblings and they with their spouses and
children a sense of completeness washes
over me but some of our loved ones are
absent from this Divine Gathering to our
astonishment some whom we believed had
accepted Christ remain unaccounted for
While others whom many of the redeemed
thought were Beyond hope have found
their place Among
Us tears of joy and sorrow Mingle for
amidst the redeemed a collective
realization Dawns upon us the absence of
loved ones friends and neighbors I think
of my best friend she isn't here after
my own conversion I would often talk to
her about the Lord she never took me
seriously but because we knew each other
from childhood we remained best friends
even though our lifestyles differ
drastically the thought of her missing
out on Heaven hurt my soul and I knew
that hurt was multiplied in infinitely
in the heart of God who was not willing
that any should perish 2 Peter
3:9 yet being in the presence of Christ
assures us that his wisdom surpasses our
limited understanding and he has made no
mistakes regarding who is lost and who
is saved the questions Among Us multiply
and intertwine reverberating through the
air as we engage in heartfelt
conversations within the vast sea of
people are those who do not yet
understand what is taking place these
had never heard of Christ but had
followed the promptings of the Holy
Spirit without knowing they lived lives
of
self-sacrifice humility and love for
neighbor these had the law written on
their hearts without having ever read or
heard of Jesus Romans 2: 14 and 15
already they were asking others about
the one wrapped in glorious fire called
Jesus and especially about the wounds in
his hands Zechariah
13:16 they will have much to learn and
understand and will be overwhelmed with
amazement as they hear the history of
the man that has purchased their
salvation from the grave it is the first
hour of Eternity anticipation is
coursing through our veins fueling our
curiosity about the Wonders that lie
ahead as we Traverse the cosmos at the
speed of light time seems to stand still
allowing us to Marvel at the
breathtaking wonders of the universe as
if on a Celestial train ride toward
Everlasting
Glory